Guide to the Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm, 1918-1965
Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm, 1918-1965
5901 mf
Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor
10 microfilm reels
Reports, pamphlets, correspondence, microfilm.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
U.S. Department of Labor; Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
SERIES LIST
Series Survey Schedules,
Series War Industry Communities Survey - Subject Files,
Series Program for Community Surveys,
Series Geographical Files,
CONTAINER LIST
- Unpublished study-Women in Unions in a Midwest War Industry Area, 1943-1945 (Reel 1)
- Proposed Plan for Union Survey., 1943; 1 (Reel 1)
  November 8, 1943. 24 frames.
  - Women's Participation in Union Affairs, 1943; 2 (Reel 1)
  - Union Policies and Programs regarding Women's Pay, 1943; 3 (Reel 1)
  - Seniority Policies and Practices of Local Unions, 1943; 4 (Reel 1)
  - Cost Attached to Union Membership, 1943; 5 (Reel 1)
  - Working Conditions., 1943; 6 (Reel 1)
- Women in Unions in a Mid-West War Industry Area., 1945; 7 (Reel 1)
  July 10, 1945. 6 frames.
- Brief summary of Activities in Connection with Union Women Carried On by Miss Wolfe and Mrs. Slater., 1944; 8 (Reel 1)
  August 7, 1944. 5 frames.
- Trade Union Survey (War Plant Unions--Wisconsin, Illinois, and Indiana), Book 1, part I., 9 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 73 frames.
  - List of Unions in Survey, 10 (Reel 1)
  - Equal Pay, 11 (Reel 1)
  - Employment of Women and Seniority, 12 (Reel 1)
  - Trade Union Survey (War Plant Unions--Wisconsin, Illinois, and Indiana), Book 1, Part II., 13 (Reel 1)
    n.d. 66 frames.
  - Women's Interest and Participation in Union Activities, 14 (Reel 1)
  - Working Condition, 15 (Reel 1)
  - Community Service, 16 (Reel 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Includes Absenteeism, Racial Discrimination, New jobs for Women, and Labor Management Committee), 17 (Reel 1)
  - Educational Work with Unions by Women's Bureau, 18 (Reel 1)
  - International Union Policies, 19 (Reel 1)
  - Contract Provisions, 20 (Reel 1)
  - List of Unions by Schedule Number., 21 (Reel 1)
- Correspondence--1943: Conference with Miss Christman on Union Survey., 22 (Reel 1)
  November 11, 1943. 3 frames
- Trade Union Survey (Suggestions for Filling Out Schedule)., 1943; 23 (Reel 1)
  November 20, 1943. 1 frame.
- Preliminary Work on Union Survey., 1943; 24 (Reel 1)
  November 13, 1943. 1 frame.
- Trade Union Survey (Contract Data to be Supplied Field Agents by Women's Bureau Officers)., 1943; 25 (Reel 1)
  November 19, 1943. 1 frame.
- Digest of Contract., 1943; 26 (Reel 1)
  December 2, 1943. 3 frames.
- Preliminary Work on Union Survey., 1943; 27 (Reel 1)
- Information Desired from Unions with War Labor Board Cases., 1943; 28 (Reel 1)
  November 10, 1943. 4 frames.
- Newspaper Clipping ("Women Making Good as Welders, Asserts Labor Bureau Report")., 1943; 29 (Reel 1)
  November 2, 1943. 1 frame.
- Letter from Agnes O'Connor to Miss Anderson regarding Industrial Condenser Corporation Case before War Labor Board., 1943; 30 (Reel 1)
  November 2, 1943. 3 frames.
- National War Labor Booard Case in the Matter of the Cudahy Packing Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL., 1943; 31 (Reel 1)
  October 20, 1943. 2 frames.
- Letter from Agnes O'Connor to Miss Anderson regarding L.S. August and Company Department Store Case before War Labor Board., 1943; 32 (Reel 1)
  October 30, 1943. 1 frames.
- Sixth Regional War Labor Board Case in the Matter of Sangamo Electric Company, 1943; 33 (Reel 1)
- War Labor Board Case in the Matter of Feltex Corporation and the United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America. CIO, 34 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 4 frames.
- Westinghouse Agreement with United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO., 35 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 1 frame.
- General Electric Agreement with the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO., 36 (Reel 1)
- Letter from the International Union, UAW Welcoming Local Union No. 6 (Buck Aviation Division)., 1943; 37 (Reel 1)
  October 1943. 1 frame.
- Agreement between Wheelco Company, Chicago and Local 1150, United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO., 1943; 38 (Reel 1)
  July 30, 1943. 4 frames.
- Proposed Plan for Union Survey., 1943; 39 (Reel 1)
  November 8, 1943. 1 frame.
- Sixth Regional War Labor Board Case in the Matter of the Grigoleit Company., 1943; 40 (Reel 1)
  August 17, 1943. 2 frames.
- National War Labor Board Report on Recommendation Wage an dSalary Adjustment Application., 1943; 41 (Reel 1)
  August 14, 1943. 4 frames.
- Handwritten Notes regarding Allies Chalmers Manufacturing Company Case before the War Labor Board., 42 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 6 frames.
- Sixth Regional War Labor Board Case in the Matter of Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and the United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers, CIO., 1943; 43 (Reel 1)
  August 3, 1943. 4 frames.
- Letter from Agnes O'Connor to Miss Anderson regarding Speech before a Machinists Local 1696., 1943; 44 (Reel 1)
  November 4, 1943. 1 frame.
- Report of Machinists Locals in Chicago by Agnes O'Connor., 1943; 45 (Reel 1)
  November 3, 1943. 6 frames.
- Letter from Agnes O'Connor regarding Contract and Wage Classification Schedules for the International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, CIO, Local 758., 1943; 46 (Reel 1)
  October 19, 1943. 1 frame.
- Letter from Agnes O'Connor regarding Contract of Machinists Local 1696., 1943; 47 (Reel 1)
  October 19, 1943. 2 frames.
- Newspaper Clippings ("UAW Faces Fight on Floor" and "Norge Job Upturn After War Seen")., 48 (Reel 1)
- Correspondence--1944: Note to Miss Spring from Miss Frieda Miller regarding schedule approval from Central Statistical Bureau., 49 (Reel 1)
  August 12, 1944. 1 frame.
- Office Memorandum from Miss Frieda Miller to Miss Spring regarding Trade Union Survey., 1944; 50 (Reel 1)
  December 12, 1944. 2 frames.
- Memorandum regarding Women's Bureau Trade Union Cooperation Plan., 1944; 51 (Reel 1)
  September 8, 1944. 5 frames.
- Agenda for Conference on Union Studies., 1944; 52 (Reel 1)
  August 10, 1944. 3 frames.
- Brief Summary of Trade Union Survey., 53 (Reel 1)
- Brief Summary of Activities in Connection with Union Women Carried on by Miss Wolfe and Mrs. Sator., 1944; 54 (Reel 1)
  August 7, 1944. 2 frames.
- Memorandum from Miss Frieda Miller to Miss Spring regarding Trade Union Study., 1944; 55 (Reel 1)
  August 9, 1944. 1 frames.
- Memorandum from Miss Frieda Miller to Miss Bertha Nienburg regarding Re-Approval of the Women in Trade Unions Study by the Budget Bureau., 1944; 56 (Reel 1)
  July 25, 1944. 2 frames.
- Memorandum from Berta Nienburg to Miss Frieda Miller regarding Status of Trade Union Study., 1944; 57 (Reel 1)
  July 22, 1944. 1 frame.
- Coverage of Local Union Survey., 1944; 58 (Reel 1)
  February 17, 1944. 2 frames.
- Memorandum from Miss I. A. Spring to Miss Frieda Miller regarding Women's Trade Union Study., 1944; 59 (Reel 1)
  July 28, 1944. 2 frames.
- Memorandum from Miss Mary Anderson to Miss Florence Paterson regarding an Estimate of Women Membership in Labor Unions., 1944; 60 (Reel 1)
  March 21, 1944. 1 frame.
- Letter from Miss Mary Anderson to Miss, 1944; 61 (Reel 1)
  May Bagwell and Mrs. Agnes O'Connor regarding Clearing of Women's Bureau Union Schedule with the Central Statistical Board. March 17, 1944. 2 frames.
- Brief Summary of Trade Union Survey., 62 (Reel 1)
- Comments on Equal Pay for Women., 63 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 3 frames.
- Extracts from Contracts and Schedules on Seniority Rights., 64 (Reel 1)
- Memorandum from Alice Angus to Miss Frieda Miller regarding Background and History of the Trade Union Survey., 1944; 65 (Reel 1)
  July 26, 1944. 1 frame.
- A Brief Resume of Some Recent Work of the Women's Bureau in Cooperation with Trade Unions to Promote the Welfare of the Working Women., 1944; 66 (Reel 1)
  June 10, 1944. 4 frames.
- Outline of Topics of Special Importance to Women Found in Union Contracts., 1944; 67 (Reel 1)
  February 19, 1944. 2 frames.
- Newspaper Clipping ("Special Privilege in Jobs Opposed")., 1944; 68 (Reel 1)
  December 9, 1944. 1 frame.
- Resolution Against the Equal Rights Amendment and for Protection of Women Workers at CIO Convention in Chicago., 1944; 69 (Reel 1)
  November 1944. 1 frame.
- War Labor Board, 1944; 70 (Reel 1)
  Decisions on Women's Pay. January 1944. 7 frames.
- Women's Bureau Suggested Standards regarding Discrimination Based on Sex or Marital Status., 1944; 71 (Reel 1)
  February 21, 1944. 3 frames.
- Some Points to Consider in Drafting Standards for Contracts., 1944; 72 (Reel 1)
  February 19, 1944. 3 frames.
- Handwritten Notes for Discussion of Equal Pay Clauses in Union Contracts., 1944; 73 (Reel 1)
  February 22, 1944. 1 frame.
- Letter from Mary Anderson to Mrs. Agnes O'Connor regarding Request for Brief Digests of Contracts from Bureau of Labor Statistics Files., 1944; 74 (Reel 1)
  February 7, 1944. 4 frames.
- Postcard Containting Description and Application for Altgeld Gardens, A Modern Community for War Workers Operated by the Chicago Housing Authoricy., 75 (Reel 1)
- Correspondence--1945: Women's Bureau Pamphlet on Union Practices and Programs., 76 (Reel 1)
  8 frames.
- Pamphlet Entitled "Union Provisions for Maternity Leave for Women Members.", 1945; 77 (Reel 1)
  4 frames.
- Women's Bureau Preliminary Survey of Women in Labor Unions in the Midwest War Industry Area., 78 (Reel 1)
- Women's Bureau Survey of Women in Unions., 1945; 79 (Reel 1)
  April 3, 1945. 6 frames.
- Comparisons of Average Hourly Earnings of Women and Men., 1945; 80 (Reel 1)
  January 1945. 3 frames.
- Forms and Instructions: Handwritten Note ("Miss A's Letter to National Unions and Replies")., 81 (Reel 1)
- Handwritten List of Unions, Their Addresses, and the Names of Their Presidents., 82 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 1 frames.
- Letter to International Unions on Equal Pay., 1945; 83 (Reel 1)
  November 17, 1945. 1 frame.
- Letter from Grant W. Oakes. President of the United Farm Equipment & Metal Workers of America, CIO to Mary Anderson on the Subject of Equal Pay for Women., 1943; 84 (Reel 1)
  November 19, 1943. 3 frames.
- Letter from H.W. Brown, President of the International Assocation of Machinists, to Mary Anderson regarding the Union's Policy on Equal Pay for Women., 1943; 85 (Reel 1)
  November 22, 1943. 1 frame.
- Letter from Ed J. Brown, President of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, to Mary Anderson regarding the Union's Policy on Equal Pay for Women., 1943; 86 (Reel 1)
- Letter from R.J. Thomas, President of the International Union, UAW-CIO, to Mary Anderson regarding the Union's Policy on Equal Pay for Women., 1943; 87 (Reel 1)
  November 24, 1943. 1 frame.
- Tentative Instructions for Union Survey., 1944; 88 (Reel 1)
  February 23, 1944. 44 frames
- Questions as to Women Leaders in Unions., 1946; 89 (Reel 1)
  December 15, 1946. 2 frames.
- List of Agreements: List of Union Agreements., 1941-1943; 90 (Reel 1)
  November 13, 1943. 4 frames.
- List of Contracts: Current Contracts of the United Electrical Workers, CIO., 91 (Reel 1)
- Current Contracts of the UAW-CIO., 92 (Reel 1)
- Current Contracts of the United Electrical Workers, AFL., 93 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 2 frames.
- Current Contracts of the International Association of Machinists, AF of L., 94 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 5 frames.
- Current Contracts Bureau of Labor Statistics Analyzed by Mrs. Agnes O'Connor., 95 (Reel 1)
- List of Plants Scheduled by Women's Bureau., 96 (Reel 1)
- Current Contracts of the United Electrical Workers, CIO., 97 (Reel 1)
- Current Contracts of the UAW-CIO., 98 (Reel 1)
- Current Contracts of the United Electrical Workers, AF of L., 99 (Reel 1)
- Current Contracts of the International Association of Machinists, AF of L., 100 (Reel 1)
- List of Tables: List of Plants Scheduled by Women's Bureau., 101 (Reel 1)
- Women's Bureau Firm Schedule Form., 102 (Reel 1)
- Equal Pay--Union Survey: Handwritten Notes and Charts Containing Information on Unions and Their Policies Toward Women (Topics Include Sex Discrimination, Equal Pay, Seniority, and Contract Provisions regarding Rest and Lunch Periods and Health and Sa@@F, 103 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 33 frames.
- Trade Union Survey--Number of Unions Covered by State, Area and Town., 104 (Reel 1)
- Handwritten Charts Dealing with Number of Years Women have been Union Members, Union @@Fees and Dues, Equal Pay for Women, WOmen on Production in Normal Times, Seniority of Women, Union Programs for Increasing Women's Participation in Union Activities, T, 105 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 53 frames.
- List of Unions: Directory of Labor Unions., 1944; 106 (Reel 1)
  February 1944. 14 frames.
- Unions Covered to Date in Women's Bureau Survey., 1944; 107 (Reel 1)
  August 15, 1944. 1 frame.
- Unions Covered to Date in Women's Bureau Survey., 1944; 108 (Reel 1)
  September 23, 1944. 1 frame.
- Trade Union Survey, CIO (List of Unions, Plants, and Products.), 109 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey, AFL (List of Unions, Plants, and Products.), 110 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey, CIO (List of Unions, Plants, and Products.), 111 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey, AFL (List of Unions, Plants, and Products.), 112 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey, CIO (List of Unions, Plants, and Products.), 113 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey, AFL (List of Unions, Plants, and Products.), 114 (Reel 1)
- Charts Showing Number of Local Unions and Plants for both AF of L and CIO., 115 (Reel 1)
- Chart, 116 (Reel 1)
  Giving Information regarding Name and Address of Plant; Name, Affiliation, and Number of Union Local; Date of Interviews; and the Names of Union Officers and Women Members Interviewed. n.d. 7 frames.
- Trade Union Survey--Number of Unions Covered by State, Area, and Town., 117 (Reel 1)
- Unions Covered to Date in Women's Bureau Study., 1944; 118 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey, CIO., 119 (Reel 1)
  Charts Containing Schedule Numbers; Date of Survey; Union Name, Number, and Location; War Labor Board Case; and Products Manufactured. n.d. 1 frame.
- Trade Union Survey, AF of L (Charts Containing Schedule Numbers, 120 (Reel 1)
- Trade Union Survey--List of Unions to Be Contacted., 1943; 121 (Reel 1)
  November 10, 1943. 1 frame.
- Materials: Table of Contents., 122 (Reel 1)
- General Comments (Including Attitude of Company toward Women Workers and Union Attitude toward Women, Union Costs, Union Educational Programs, Union Office Holding, Male and @@Female Classification of Jobs, Maternity Leave, Child Care, Shifts Determined, 123 (Reel 1)
- Summary of War Labor Board Cases., 124 (Reel 1)
- Summaries of Trade Union Survey., 125 (Reel 1)
- Questions regarding Equal Pay., 126 (Reel 1)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics Survey--Handwritten Chart relating to Female Sewing Machine Operators., 1943; 127 (Reel 1)
  July 1943. 1 frame.
- Women's Bureau Pamphlet Entitled "Work for Women after the War.", 128 (Reel 1)
- Job Evaluations--A.O. Smith Corporation, Milwaukee, WI (Agreed to by Smith Steel Workers Union 19806 and Approved by War Labor Board)., 129 (Reel 1)
  n.d. 14 frames.
- Women's Bureau Pamphlet on Union Practices and Programs Entitled "Rate for the Job.", 1945; 130 (Reel 1)
  5 frames.
- Women's Bureau Suggested Standards for Union Contract Provisions Affecting Women., 131 (Reel 1)
- Handwritten Notes regarding Union Membership and List of Cities., 132 (Reel 1)
- Women's Bureau Pamphlet Entitled "Work for Women after the War.", 133 (Reel 1)
- Women's Bureau Pamphlet Entitled "Equal Pay--A Progress Report.", 1944; 134 (Reel 1)
  May 1944. 4 frames.
- Trade Union Study--Outline., 135 (Reel 1)
- Women's Bureau Suggested Standards for Union Contract Provisions Affecting Women (two copies)., 1944; 136 (Reel 1)
  March 1944. 8 frames.
- Handwritten Notes regarding Dispute between the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 1102 and the Emerson Electric and manufacturing Company., 1941; 137 (Reel 1)
  August 1941. 4 frames.
- US Department of Labor Pamphlet and the Status of Women in Unions in War Plants--Seniority., 1945; 138 (Reel 1)
  3 frames.
- Women's Bureau Pamhplet Entitled "Rate for the Job.", 1945; 139 (Reel 1)
- Women's Bureau Recommendations on Union Provisions for Maternity Leave for Women's Members., 1945; 140 (Reel 1)
  2 frames.
- Unpublished study-Women in Unions in a Midwest War Industry Area, 1943-1945 (continued) (Reel 2)
- Agreements: Agreement between the United States Rubber Company, Indianapolis Plant and the United Rubber Workers of America, Local Union Number 110., 1943; 1 (Reel 2)
  May 1, 1943. 19 frames.
- Agreement between the Continental Roll and Steel Foundry Company, East Chicago Division and Federal Labor Union Number 22636 of the AF of L., 1942; 2 (Reel 2)
  November 10, 1942. 11 frames.
- Agreement between the Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation and the United Steelworkers of America, CIO., 1942; 3 (Reel 2)
  September 1, 1942. 30 frames.
- Agreement between the Allis-Chalmers ManufacturingCompany and the Allis-Chalmers Workers' Union, Local 248 of the UAW-CIO., 1943; 4 (Reel 2)
  37 frames.
- Agreement between the Anaconda Wire & Cable Company and Federal Labor Union Number 18704 of the AF of L., 1943; 5 (Reel 2)
  July 1, 1943. 6 frames.
- Working Agreement with the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 212, Detroit, MI and Local No. 265, Evansville, IN., 1942; 6 (Reel 2)
  November 13, 1942. 22 frames.
- Agreement between the International Union, UAW-CIO and the Chrysler Corporation., 1943; 7 (Reel 2)
  September 10, 1943. 21 frames.
- Agreement between West Pullman Works, International Harvester Company and West Pullman Local No. 107, UFE&MWA [United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America]--CIO., 1942; 8 (Reel 2)
  May 12, 1942. 26 frames.
- Smith Steel Workers Union Local No. 19806 Contract., 1943-1944; 9 (Reel 2)
  12 frames.
- Agreement between the Briggs & Stratten Corporation and Local Union No. 232 of the International Union, United Automobile Workers, AF of L., 1942; 10 (Reel 2)
  September 17, 1942. 18 frames.
- Contract and Agreement between Local 736, UAW-CIO and Automatic Products Company, Milwaukee, WI., 1942; 11 (Reel 2)
  August 14, 1942. 8 frames.
- Agreement between the General Electric X-Ray Corporation and the International Association of Machinists, Local 1696., 1943; 12 (Reel 2)
  September 20, 1943. 10 frames.
- Rules, Union Contract and Group Insurance Plan for the Chicago Telephone Supply Company and the UAW-CIO, Local No. 941., 1942; 13 (Reel 2)
  November 24, 1942. 18 frames.
- Agreement between the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 and Foundry Unit, Indianapolis Works, International Harvester Company., 1942; 14 (Reel 2)
  June 23, 1942. 20 frames.
- Contract between the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 and the Prest-O-Lite Battery Company, Indianapolis, IN., 1944; 15 (Reel 2)
  April 19, 1944. 17 frames.
- Agreement between the McQuay-Norris Manufacturing Company, Indianapolis Division Plant and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 226., 1943; 16 (Reel 2)
  December 31, 1943. 12 frames.
- Agreement between P.R. Mallory & Company, Inc. and the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 1001., 1942; 17 (Reel 2)
  May 22, 1942. 14 frames.
- Agreement between Republic Aviation Corporation, Indiana Division and Local Union No. 492, UAW-CIO., 1944; 18 (Reel 2)
  January 21, 1944. 28 frames.
- Agreement between the Marmon-Herrington Company, Inc. and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 226., 1943; 19 (Reel 2)
  June 22, 1943. 18 frames.
- Agreement between the Bendix Products Division, Bendix Aviation Corporation of South Bend, IN and Local Union No. 9, UAW-CIO., 1942; 20 (Reel 2)
  Febrnuary 1, 1942. 21 frames.
- Agreement between Bendix Home Appliances, Inc. of South Bend, IN and Bendix Local No. 9, UAW-CIO., 1941; 21 (Reel 2)
  April 29, 1941. 14 frames.
- Agreement between the Excel Curtain Company, Inc. and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 764., 1942; 22 (Reel 2)
  January 1, 1942. 10 frames.
- Agreement between the Sunbeam Electric Manufacturing Company and Local No. 813 of the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO., 1942; 23 (Reel 2)
  December 22, 1942. 11 frames.
- Agreement between C.G. Conn, Ltd. and the United Musical Instrument Workers, Local Union No. 1050., 1942; 24 (Reel 2)
  November 5, 1942. 10 frames.
- Agreement between the Studebaker Corporation of South Bend, IN and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 5., 1937; 25 (Reel 2)
  May 21, 1937. 21 frames.
- Contract Covering the Agreement between the East Moline Works, International Harvester Company and Local No. 104, UFE[&M]WA, CIO., 1942; 26 (Reel 2)
  May 11, 1942. 22 frames.
- Agreement between the Feltex Corporation (Fiber Container Division), Rock Island, Illinois and the Farm Equipment Workers' Organizing Committee, CIO., 1942; 27 (Reel 2)
  July 8, 1942. 9 frames.
- Agreement between the Missouri Valley Bridge & Iron Company (Shipbuilding Division) and the Metal Trades Department of the AF of L, The Evansville Metal Trades Council, and Their Affiliates for Evansville Shipyard., 1942; 28 (Reel 2)
  June 8, 1942. 23 frames.
- Agreement between the Pierce Governor Company and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local No. 940., 1943; 29 (Reel 2)
  June 19, 1943. 18 frames.
- Agreement between the Bridgeport Brass Ordnance Plant and the International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, CIO, Local No. 607., 1944; 30 (Reel 2)
  April 15, 1944. 12 frames.
- Contract Between Local 81, UAW-CIO and the Union Malleable Iron Company of Deere & Company., 1943; 31 (Reel 2)
  March 22, 1943. 23 frames.
- Contract between Local 865, UAW-CIO and the John Deere Harvester Works of East Moline, Illinois., 1943; 32 (Reel 2)
  Febrnuary 18, 1943. 25 frames.
- Agreement between the J.I. Case Company, Rock Island Works and Local 806, UAW-CIO., 1943; 33 (Reel 2)
  April 29, 1943. 16 frames.
- Agreement between the East Moline Works of the International Harvester Company and the United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local Union No. 156., 1943; 34 (Reel 2)
  November 17, 1943. 22 frames.
- Agreement between the Eagle Signal Company of Moline, Illinois and Local 814 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America., 1943; 35 (Reel 2)
  June 29, 1943. 20 frames.
- Agreement between the Caterpillar Tractor Company of Peoria, Illinois and the United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local 105., 1942; 36 (Reel 2)
  September 22, 1942. 7 frames.
- Agreement between the Dole Valve Company and the International Union, UAW-CIO, Local Union No. 278., 1944; 37 (Reel 2)
  15 frames.
- Agreement between Local Union No. 112 of the UFE & MWA and the Oliver South Bend Plant No. 1., 38 (Reel 2)
  n.d. 7 frames.
- Contract Changes in Agreement between C.G. Conn, Ltd. of Elkhart, IN and U.A. Local 534, CIO., 1943; 39 (Reel 2)
  July 12, 1943. 5 frames.
- Agreement between the United States Rubber Company, Ball-Band Plant, Mishawaka, IN and Local No. 65 of the United Rubber Workers of America., 1942; 40 (Reel 2)
  August 5, 1942. 9 frames.
- Agreement between the Electro-Voice Manufacturing Company of South Bend, IN and Local 927 of the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America., 1944; 41 (Reel 2)
  Febrnuary 14, 1944. 7 frames.